That mother doesn't go to our house to have sex,
you guys go somewhere outside to have sex
.
Hey, if your uncle told you to go outside, you
would have locked the door and stayed there.
Do something, there's
only one idea for this.
Dad, should we go to the swimming pool or should we leave without
asking you?
I'm jolly jolly jolly, success, I'm at the
swimming pool.
Okay, I'll buy a flight ticket and come back.
Uncle, jump, uncle.  I want to jump, I
want to jump too, but I can't jump, all the water is coming up
.   It's
so confusing. You've been
kicked by a sinner.
The tube you listened to
[music]
[music][bell] Well,
lake, swimming pool.
Tell me in the comments where you like to bathe. Is
everyone happy? It was great. Thanks,
uncle. I'll come next week, uncle.
[laughter]